Mathew Harvey

Web Developer

Contact

Address

Perth, WA, 6000

Phone

040 893 0300

E-mail

mathewharvey@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mathew-harvey-0b778626

Skills

Website optimization

Agile Workflow

Video File Editing

Technical Writing

Project Management

Organization

Software

Html

CSS

Java Script

Full stack web developer, scientist with extensive project management experience, educated at Griffith University and The University of Western Australia (Bachelor Science). Skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and strengths in meeting deadlines, creativity, and teamwork. I have built all aspects of and then successfully ran a brick and mortar and online business (www.thebodyweightgym.net).

I am fascinated by computer science and the parallels between biological and computer systems. I love breaking down a problem piece-by-piece to find a solution. My technical aptitude, combined with my background as a scientist has led me to being adept at problem solving and makes me a strong addition to any engineering team.

Work History

2018-11 -Current

Web Developer

The Bodyweight Gym, Perth, WA
I created and manage www.thebodyweightgym.net.
Leading a team of 3 other developers I developed The
Bodyweight Gym Online - a online training platform https://www.thebodyweightgym.net/the-bodyweightgym-online. As part of these roles I complete the
following:

- Oversaw technical issues and troubleshooting requests to resolve surfaced problems.
- Employed JSQuery and other technology to make line-code repairs and optimize corporate presence.
- Developed functional digital design concepts across various platforms to strengthen company brand and identity.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages, plugins and functionality for continuous improvement.
- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability, security and specialized scripts.

2017-07 -Current

Managing Director

The Bodyweight Gym, Perth, WA
I founded and built The Bodyweight Gym and The
Bodyweight Gym Online

(www.thebodyweightgym.net/the-bodyweightgym-online). I currently manage the business along with its 5 employees and act as, head coach and personal trainer.

2016-01 -2017-04

Principle Environmental Scientist

Boskalis, Scarborough, WA

Managed environmental legal considerations associated with dredging within the Inpex Ichthys project based out of Darwin. I managed a state level audit, leasing between Inpex and state and federal regulators.

2015-01 -2017-01

Senior Environmental Scientst

Auricon, Brisbane, QLD

I managed an team of scientist through an federal and state level EIS for the Port of Gladstone dredging project.

Education

Bachelor of Science

Griffith University - Gold Coast

2020-06 -Current Certificate: Full Stack Web Development

University Of Western Australia - Perth

2013-06 -2014-06 **Diploma of Supervisory Managment:**

Personal Management

School Of Management Australia - Brisbane

Hobbies

I enjoy building and racing FPV drones